http://www.meinlpercussion.com/en/privacy-policy

KKalimbasMMalletsMaracasMicrophone ClampsPPandeirosPercussion Stomp BoxesPickup InstrumentsRRainmakers/RainsticksRitual DrumsSSambaShakersShekeresSleigh BellsSound EffectsStandsSticksScrapersSurdosTTablasTablesTamborimsTambourinesTampeiroTimbalesTrianglesWWood Frogsall productsNEW PRODUCTSall productsCajonsDjembesCongasBongosTimbalesCowbellsPickup InstrumentsFrame DrumsTambourinesDidgeridoos & RainmakersDarbukas & DoumbeksIbo DrumsRitual DrumsHand PercussionFoot PercussionSound EffectsCymbalsSurdosBagsHardwareHIGHLIGHTSSLEIGH BELLARTISAN TANGO LINE CAJON - LimbaMicrophone Clampspickup KalimbaALL NEW PRODUCTSCajonsall CajonsDjembesall DjembesCongasall CongasBongosall BongosTimbalesall TimbalesCowbellsall CowbellsPickup Instrumentsall Pickup InstrumentsFrame Drumsall Frame DrumsTambourinesall TambourinesDidgeridoos & Rainmakersall Didgeridoos & RainmakersDarbukas & Doumbeksall Darbukas & DoumbeksIbo Drumsall Ibo DrumsRitual Drumsall Ritual DrumsHand Percussionall Hand PercussionFoot Percussionall Foot PercussionSound Effectsall Sound EffectsCymbalsall CymbalsSurdosall SurdosBagsall BagsHardwareall HardwarePRODUCT CHANNELVisit our MEINL YouTube channel with the latest videos of our products.YouTubeMEINL Percussion | Alpine Series Djembe | Day of the Dead
Exclusive Meinl Percussion Content
Get inside info on percussion, sounds, your favourite Meinl artists, Meinl global events, and more.
show all Topics
Our latest Topics
Studio Session - Behind The Scenes
Stephan Emig
Alexandra Alban &amp; Diego Camacho
"Inka Latin"
Microphone Clamps
Our MEINL Microphone Clamps are flexible and give you the ability to..
Kalimbas
Also known as a thumb piano, these instruments create soothing melodic tones...
Search:
Privacy Policy
The protection of your privacy is very important to us, in the following we inform you in detail about how we handle your data.1. ControllerRoland Meinl Musikinstrumente GmbH & Co. KG, Musik-Meinl-Str. 1, 91468 Gutenstetten, seat and register court: District Court HRA 6513 is the provider of the website www.meinl.de and responsible for data processing in relation to the use of the website.1.1 General informationWe take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Therefore, we treat your personal data confidentially and in accordance with the legal data protection regulations and this data protection declaration. When you use this website, various personal data is collected. Personal data is data with which you can be personally identified. This data protection declaration explains which data we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this is done. We would like to point out that data transmission on the Internet (e.g. communication by e-mail) can have security vulnerabilities. A complete protection of data against access by third parties is not possible.1.2 Data Protection OfficerWe have appointed a data protection officer who is responsible for questions relating to this privacy policy. If you have any questions regarding this data protection declaration, you can contact our data protection officer at the following address.Michael WeissIT - Consulting & Datenschutz
Am Schind 14 - 97514 Oberaurach
E-Mail: datenschutzbeauftragter@meinl.de2. Your RightsYou have the right to receive information free of charge about the origin, recipient and purpose of your stored personal data. You also have the right to demand the correction or deletion of this data. For this purpose, as well as for further questions on data protection, you can contact us or our data protection officer at any time. Furthermore, you have the right to complain to the responsible supervisory authority. Furthermore, you have the right to demand under certain circumstances the restriction of the processing of your personal data. For details, please refer to the data protection declaration under "2.2 Right to limit processing".2.1 Information about, rectification and eradication of dataWithin the scope of the applicable statutory provisions, you have the right to at any time demand information about your archived personal data, their source and recipients as well as the purpose of the processing of your data. You may also have a right to have your data rectified or eradicated. If you have questions about this subject matter or any other questions about personal data, please do not hesitate to contact us at any time at the address provided in section “Information Required by Law.”2.2 Right to demand processing restrictionsYou have the right to demand the imposition of restrictions as far as the processing of your personal data is concerned. To do so, you may contact us at any time at the address provided in section “Information Required by Law.” The right to demand restriction of processing applies in the following cases:In the event that you should dispute the correctness of your data archived by us, we will usually need some time to verify this claim. During the time that this investigation is ongoing, you have the right to demand that we restrict the processing of your personal data. If the processing of your personal data was/is conducted in an unlawful manner, you have the option to demand the restriction of the processing of your data in lieu of demanding the eradication of this data.If we do not need your personal data any longer and you need it to exercise, defend or claim legal entitlements, you have the right to demand the restriction of the processing of your personal data instead of its eradication.If you have raised an objection pursuant to Art. 21 Sect. 1 GDPR, your rights and our rights will have to be weighed against each other. As long as it has not been determined whose interests prevail, you have the right to demand a restriction of the processing of your personal data.If you have restricted the processing of your personal data, these data – with the exception of their archiving – may be processed only subject to your consent or to claim, exercise or defend legal entitlements or to protect the rights of other natural persons or legal entities or for important public interest reasons cited by the European Union or a member state of the EU.2.3 Right to object to the collection of data in special cases; right to object to direct advertisingIn the event that data are processed on the basis of Art. 6 sect. 1 lit. E or F GDPR, you have the right to at any time object to the processing of your personal data based on grounds arising from your unique situation. This also applies to any profiling based on these provisions. To determine the legal basis, on which any processing of data is based, please consult this data protection declaration. If you log an objection, we will no longer process your affected personal data, unless we are in a position to present compelling protection worthy grounds for the processing of your data, that outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms or if the purpose of the processing is the claiming, exercising or defence of legal entitlements (objection pursuant to Art. 21 Sect. 1 GDPR). If your personal data is being processed in order to engage in direct advertising, you have the right to at any time object to the processing of your affected personal data for the purposes of such advertising. This also applies to profiling to the extent that it is affiliated with such direct advertising. If you object, your personal data will subsequently no longer be used for direct advertising purposes (objection pursuant to Art. 21 sect. 2 GDPR).2.4 Revocation of your consent to the processing of dataA wide range of data processing transactions are possible only subject to your express consent. You can also revoke at any time any consent you have already given us. To do so, all you are required to do is sent us an informal notification via e-mail. This shall be without prejudice to the lawfulness of any data collection that occurred prior to your revocation.2.5 Right to data portabilityYou have the right to demand that we hand over any data we automatically process on the basis of your consent or in order to fulfil a contract be handed over to you or a third party in a commonly used, machine readable format. If you should demand the direct transfer of the data to another controller, this will be done only if it is technically feasible.2.6 Right to log a complaint with the competent supervisory agencyIn the event of violations of the GDPR, data subjects are entitled to log a complaint with a supervisory agency, in particular in the member state where they usually maintain their domicile, place of work or at the place where the alleged violation occurred. The right to log a complaint is in effect regardless of any other administrative or court proceedings available as legal recourses.3. Recording of data on this website3.1 Cookies3.2 Server log filesThe provider of this website and its pages automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser communicates to us automatically. The information comprises: The type and version of browser used, the used operating system, Referrer URL, the hostname of the accessing computer, the time of the server inquiry, the IP address This data is not merged with other data sources.This data is recorded on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR.3.3 Request by e-mail, telephone, fax or via contact formIf you contact us by e-mail, telephone, fax or via our contact form, your request, including all resulting personal data will be stored and processed by us for the purpose of processing your request. We do not pass these data on without your consent. The processing of these data is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR, if your request is related to the execution of a contract or if it is necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures.In all other cases, the processing is based on your consent (Article 6 (1) a GDPR) and/or on our legitimate interests (Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR), since we have a legitimate interest in the effective processing of requests addressed to us. The data sent by you to us via contact requests remain with us until you request us to delete, revoke your consent to the storage or the purpose for the data storage lapses (e.g. after completion of your request). Mandatory statutory provisions in particular statutory retention periods remain unaffected.3.4 Registration on this websiteYou have the option to register on this website to be able to use additional website functions. We shall use the data you enter only for the purpose of using the respective offer or service you have registered for. The required information we request at the time of registration must be entered in full. Otherwise we shall reject the registration. To notify you of any important changes to the scope of our portfolio or in the event of technical modifications, we shall use the e-mail address provided during the registration process. We shall process the data entered during the registration process on the basis of your consent (Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR).The data recorded during the registration process shall be stored by us as long as you are registered on this website. Subsequently, such data shall be deleted. This shall be without prejudice to mandatory statutory retention obligations.4. Hosting and Content Delivery NetworksExternal HostingThis website is hosted by an external service provider (host). Personal data collected on this website are stored on the servers of the host. These may include, but are not limited to, IP addresses, contact requests, metadata and communications, contract information, contact information, names, web page access, and other data generated through a web site.The host is used for the purpose of fulfilling the contract with our potential and existing customers (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR) and in the interest of secure, fast and efficient provision of our online services by a professional provider (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR). Our host will only process your data to the extent necessary to fulfil its performance obligations and to follow our instructions with respect to such data.Execution of a contract data processing agreement according to Art. 28 GDPRIn order to guarantee processing in compliance with data protection regulations, we have concluded an order processing contract with our host.CloudflareWe use the “Cloudflare” service provided by Cloudflare, Inc. 665 3rd St. #200, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.Cloudflare offers a content delivery network with Domain Name Service that is available worldwide. As a result, the information transfer that occurs between your browser and our website is technically routed via Cloudflare’s network. This enables Cloudflare to analyze data transactions between your browser and our website and to work as a filter between our servers and potentially malicious data traffic from the Internet.Cloudflare is also a certified participant of the “EU-US Privacy Shield Framework.” Cloudflare has undertaken to handle all personal data originating from the member states of the European Union (EU) in compliance with the “Privacy Shield Framework.” The use of Cloudflare is based on our legitimate interest in a provision of our website offerings that is as error free and secure as possible (Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR).For more information on Cloudflare’s security precautions and data privacy policies, please follow this link:https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/5. Website AnalysisWhen you visit this website, your surfing behaviour can be statistically evaluated. This is mainly done with cookies and with so-called analysis programs. The analysis of your surfing behaviour is usually anonymous; the surfing behaviour cannot be traced back to you. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. You can find detailed information about these tools and about your options to object here.5.1 Google AnalyticsThis website uses functions of the web analysis service Google Analytics. The provider of this service is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.Google Analytics uses so-called cookies. Cookies are text files, which are stored on your computer and that enable an analysis of the use of the website by users. The information generated by cookies on your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the United States, where it is stored.The storage of Google Analytics cookies and the utilization of this analysis tool are based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The operator of this website has a legitimate interest in the analysis of user patterns to optimize both, the services offered online and the operator’s advertising activities. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time.IP anonymizationOn this website, we have activated the IP anonymization function. As a result, your IP address will be abbreviated by Google within the member states of the European Union or in other states that have ratified the Convention on the European Economic Area prior to its transmission to the United States. The full IP address will be transmitted to one of Google’s servers in the United States and abbreviated there only in exceptional cases. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google shall use this information to analyse your use of this website to generate reports on website activities and to render other services to the operator of this website that are related to the use of the website and the Internet. The IP address transmitted in conjunction with Google Analytics from your browser shall not be merged with other data in Google’s possession.Browser plug-inYou do have the option to prevent the archiving of cookies by making pertinent changes to the settings of your browser software. However, we have to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website to their fullest extent. Moreover, you have the option prevent the recording of the data generated by the cookie and affiliated with your use of the website (including your IP address) by Google as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link:https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enObjection to the recording of dataYou have the option to prevent the recording of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. This will result in the placement of an opt out cookie, which prevents the recording of your data during future visits to this website:Google Analytics deactivation.For more information about the handling of user data by Google Analytics, please consult Google’s Data Privacy Declaration at:https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=enContract data processingWe have executed a contract data processing agreement with Google and are implementing the stringent provisions of the German data protection agencies to the fullest when using Google Analytics.Demographic parameters provided by Google AnalyticsThis website uses the function “demographic parameters” provided by Google Analytics. It makes it possible to generate reports providing information on the age, gender and interests of website visitors. The sources of this information are interest-related advertising by Google as well as visitor data obtained from third party providers. This data cannot be allocated to a specific individual. You have the option to deactivate this function at any time by making pertinent settings changes for advertising in your Google account or you can generally prohibit the recording of your data by Google Analytics as explained in section “Objection to the recording of data”.Archiving periodData on the user or incident level stored by Google linked to cookies, user IDs or advertising IDs (e.g. DoubleClick cookies, Android advertising ID) will be anonymized or deleted after 14 months. For details please click the following link:https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=en5.2 MatomoThis website uses the open source web analysis service Matomo. Matomo uses so-called “cookies,” which are text files that are stored on your computer and that make it possible to analyse your use of this website. In conjunction with this, the information about the use of this website generated by the cookie will be archived on our server. Prior to archiving, the IP address will first be anonymized.Matomo cookies will remain on your device until you delete them.The storage of Matomo cookies and the use of this analysis tool are based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the analysis of user patterns, in order to optimize the operator’s web offerings and advertising. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time.The information generated by cookies concerning the use of this website shall not be shared with any third parties. You may prevent the storage of cookies at any time by making pertinent changes to your browser software settings; however, we have to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website to their fullest extent. If you do not consent to the storage and use of your data, you have the option to deactivate the storage and use of such data here. In this case, an opt out cookie will be placed in our browser, which prevent the storage of usage data by Matomo. If you delete your cookies, this will also result in the deletion of the Matomo opt out cookie. Hence, you will have to reactivate the opt out when you return to visit this website.5.3 Facebook PixelTo measure conversion rates, this website uses the visitor activity pixel of Facebook. The provider of this service is Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland. According to Facebook’s statement the collected data will be transferred to the USA and other third-party countries too. This tool allows the tracking of page visitors after they have been linked to the website of the provider after clicking on a Facebook ad. This makes it possible to analyse the effectiveness of Facebook ads for statisticaland market research purposes and to optimize future advertising campaigns. For us as the operators of this website, the collected data is anonymous. We are not in a position to arrive at any conclusions as to the identity of users. However, Facebook archives the information and processes it, so that it is possible to make a connection to the respective user profile and Facebook is in a position to use the data for its own promotional purposes in compliance with the Facebook Data Usage Policy. This enables Facebook to display ads on Facebook pages as well as in locations outside of Facebook. We as the operator of this website have no control over the use of such data.The use of Facebook Pixel is based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The operator of the website has a legitimate interest in effective advertising campaigns, which also include social media. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time. In Facebook’s Data Privacy Policies, you will find additional information about the protection of your privacy at:https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/You also have the option to deactivate the remarketing function “Custom Audiences” in the ad settings section underhttps://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen. To do this, you first have to log into Facebook.If you do not have a Facebook account, you can deactivate any user-based advertising by Facebook on the website of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance:http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/praferenzmanagement/6. NewsletterIf you would like to subscribe to the newsletter offered on this website, we will need from you an e-mail address as well as information that allow us to verify that you are the owner of the e-mail address provided and consent to the receipt of the newsletter. No further data shall be collected or shall be collected only on a voluntary basis. We shall use such data only for the sending of the requested information and shall not share such data with any third parties.The processing of the information entered into the newsletter subscription form shall occur exclusively on the basis of your consent (Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR). You may revoke the consent you have given to the archiving of data, the e-mail address and the use of this information for the sending of the newsletter at any time, for instance by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the newsletter. This shall be without prejudice to the lawfulness of any data processing transactions that have taken place to date.The data deposited with us for the purpose of subscribing to the newsletter will be stored by us until you unsubscribe from the newsletter or the newsletter service provider and deleted from the newsletter distribution list after you unsubscribe from the newsletter. Data stored for other purposes with us remain unaffected.After you unsubscribe from the newsletter distribution list, your e-mail address may be stored by us or the newsletter service provider in a blacklist to prevent future mailings. The data from the blacklist is used only for this purpose and not merged with other data. This serves both your interest and our interest in complying with the legal requirements when sending newsletters (legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR). The storage in the blacklist is indefinite.7. Social-Plug-ins7.1 YouTube with expanded data protection integrationOur website embeds videos of the website YouTube. The website operator is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.We use YouTube in the expanded data protection mode. According to YouTube, this mode ensures that YouTube does not store any information about visitors to this website before they watch the video. Nevertheless, this does not necessarily mean that the sharing of data with YouTube partners can be ruled out as a result of the expanded data protection mode. For instance, regardless of whether you are watching a video, YouTube will always establish a connection with the Google DoubleClick network. As soon as you start to play a YouTube video on this website, a connection to YouTube’s servers will be established. As a result, the YouTube server will be notified, which of our pages you have visited. If you are logged into your YouTube account while you visit our site, you enable YouTube to directly allocate your browsing patterns to your personal profile. You have the option to prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. Furthermore, after you have started to play a video, YouTube will be able to place various cookies on your device. With the assistance of these cookies, YouTube will be able to obtain information about our website's visitors. Among other things, this information will be used to generate video statistics with the aim of improving the user friendliness of the site and to prevent attempts to commit fraud. These cookies will stay on your device until you delete them. Under certain circumstances, additional data processing transactions may be triggered after you have started to play a YouTube video, which are beyond our control. The use of YouTube is based on our interest in presenting our online content in an appealing manner. Pursuant to Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR, this is a legitimate interest. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time. For more information on how YouTube handles user data, please consult the YouTube Data Privacy Policy under:https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en7.2 Google Maps (with consent)This website uses Google Maps, a mapping/location service, via an API. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.To warrant data protection on this website, you will find that Google Maps has been deactivated when you visit this website for the first time. A direct connection to Google’s servers will not be established until you have activated Google Maps autonomously at your end (i.e. given your consent pursuant to Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR). This will prevent the transfer of your data to Google during your first visit to our website. Once you have activated the service, Google Maps will store your IP address. As a rule, it is subsequently transferred to a Google server in the United States, where it is stored. The provider of this website does not have any control over this data transfer once Google Maps has been activated. For more information about the handling of user data, please consult the Data Privacy Declaration of Google under the following link:https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/8. Job ApplicationsWe also offer you the opportunity to submit your application to our company electronically, e.g. by e-mail. We will of course use your details exclusively for processing your application and will not pass them on to third parties.8.1 Web formYou can also apply to our company online via our application portal. Your online application will be forwarded directly to our personnel department via an encrypted connection and will of course be treated confidentially.If we are unable to make you a job offer, you reject a job offer or withdraw your application, we reserve the right to keep the data you have submitted with us for up to 6 months from the end of the application procedure (rejection or withdrawal of the application) on the basis of our legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR).8.2 Admission to the applicant poolIf we do not make you a job offer, there may be the possibility to include you in our pool of applicants. If you are accepted, all documents and details from your application will be transferred to the applicant pool so that we can contact you in the event of suitable vacancies. Admission to the applicant pool is based solely on your express consent (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR). This consent is voluntary and has no relation to the current application procedure. This consent can be revoked at any time. In this case, the data will be irrevocably deleted from the applicant pool, provided there are no legal reasons for retention. The data from the applicant pool will be irrevocably deleted at the latest two years after consent has been granted.9. Data SecurityWe have taken extensive technical and operational precautions to protect your data from accidental or deliberate manipulation, loss, destruction or access by unauthorised persons. Our security procedures are regularly reviewed and adapted to technological progress.For security reasons and to protect the transmission of confidential content, such as purchase orders or inquiries you submit to us as the website operator, this website uses either an SSL or a TLS encryption programme. You can recognise an encrypted connection by checking whether the address line of the browser switches from “http://” to “https://” and also by the appearance of the lock icon in the browser line. If the SSL or TLS encryption is activated, data you transmit to us cannot be read by third parties.Productshighlights in 2020atmo-instrumentsArtistsServiceTopicsStompboxesCajonsDjembesBongosAlpine Series DjembesBacking TracksMicrophone ClampsKalimbasArtist Series Sand Hihat TambourineThe Meinl Groove BellMeinl Percussion - Candela Percussion CymbalsStudio Session InsightsAbout UsProductsNEW PRODUCTSall productsCajonsDjembesCongasBongosTimbalesCowbellsPickup InstrumentsFrame DrumsTambourinesDidgeridoos & RainmakersDarbukas & DoumbeksIbo DrumsRitual DrumsHand PercussionFoot PercussionSound EffectsCymbalsSurdosBagsHardwareTopics
Exclusive Meinl Percussion Content
Get inside info on percussion, sounds, your favourite Meinl artists, Meinl global events, and more.
show all Topics
Our latest Topics
Studio Session - Behind The Scenes
Stephan Emig
Alexandra Alban &amp; Diego Camacho
"Inka Latin"
Microphone Clamps
Our MEINL Microphone Clamps are flexible and give you the ability to..
Kalimbas
Also known as a thumb piano, these instruments create soothing melodic tones...
Meinl BrandsThe leading developer of percussion instrumentsmeinlpercussion.comMEINL Cymbals inspire drummers from all around the worldmeinlcymbals.comHigh-Quality Drum Sticks, Brushes, Multi-Rods and moremeinlstickandbrush.comSound Therapeutic Instruments
for Individualistsmeinlsonicenergy.commusical instruments designed specifically for childrenninopercussion.comsophisticated Drum Circle instruments for everyonemeinlvivarhythm.comAcoustic instruments for the modern-day player since 1994ortegaguitars.com
